20:38 Shibuya Hikarie B3F
Well, this is awful.
There's another veil centered underneath
here that also traps non-sorcerers inside.
Hey, pardon me.
Hup, hup.
I think I have a good idea what they're after.
I'll play along.
20:39 Aoyama Cemetery
They're making Gojo-sensei do this alone?!
I understand the logic, but there
has to be something we can do, too!
Be his backup or something!
Huh?
Yeah. That's why we're heading to Shibuya now.
Oh, we are?
Give it back.
"Give it back"?
Forcing Nee-sama to be his backup...
Satoru Gojo must think he's some big-shot.
You shouldn't treat him
like some ordinary guy.
You're not like ordinary
women yourself, Nee-sama.
Some Ordinary Guy
Ah, Ui Ui!
You truly are adorable!
There you go saying stuff
you don't believe again.
Team Mei Mei\h\hMei Mei (Grade 1 Jujutsu Sorcerer)\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hUi Ui\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hYuji Itadori (Promotion Evaluation Postponed)
What you love isn't family, but work
relations treated as family relations, right?
You really do get it.
I love that part of you.
Oh, my!
Let's hurry up and go.
Hello, Mei Mei here.
Oh?
Itadori-kun, change in destination.
Huh?
Another veil like the one over Shibuya
was lowered over Meiji Shrine Station.
We're heading to that one.
We're running. Keep up.
Right!
20:40\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTokyo Metro, Shibuya Station
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hB5F, Shin-toshin Line Platform
I see you're all fully prepared.
You came.
You won't have any excuses left
when you lose this time.
And have you given thought to the
first excuse you'll use when you lose?
Episode 32
The Shibuya Incident
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Platform
There's a veil to keep
ordinary people trapped inside
covering the entire
underground subway station,
and within that, there's another
veil centered around the platform
20:51 \h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTokyo Metro, Meiji Shrine Station
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hExit 2
on level B5 that prevents
sorcerers from entering.
We believe the cursed spirit or
curse user who lowered these veils
is located somewhere between these two.
Between them?
Not on the platform they're centered around?
We believe they're most likely taking
on the risk of being outside
the veil as well in order
to strengthen the barrier.
Two of our assistant supervisors
have already been taken out.
Also, in between these barriers...
Well, we can't say for certain yet, but...
That's fine. Say it.
There are transfigured
humans between the barriers.
What are you two doing?! We have to hurry!
Shh!
Nee-sama is currently sharing
the crows' perception.
It's a process that takes
concentration, so be quiet.
I don't mind if you talk.
She says it's fine.
Oh, Nee-sama!
Yeah.
I've got the gist of it.
Itadori-kun,
which would you prefer?
Killing lots of weak, transfigured humans,
or exorcising one powerful cursed spirit?
Knowing you, it's probably the latter.
This is a map of the underground station.
The transfigured humans are mulling about
and attacking normal people here, on level B4.
The majority of the normal people are
probably at the train platform on level B5.
"Probably"?
The crows I used are imbued
with cursed energy,
so they couldn't enter B5.
I'm guessing they're forcing normal people
to flee to B5, and serving them up.
Also, my crows got hunted
down here, between B1 and B2.
This is likely where the cursed spirit
or curse user who lowered the veil is.
Maybe they're planning to hunt down
any common people that come back up,
or maybe it has something to do
with the veils' conditions,
but it's unclear why they've chosen
this positioning, and what they hope
to achieve by isolating level B5.
He's here, though, right?
Right below us.
That curse.
Maybe?
My crows all got killed before they
could confirm seeing Patchface.
Though the presence of transfigured
humans would suggest that's likely.
I'm not so sure about dividing up our forces,
but if we keep wasting time, all the
common people on B4 will be wiped out.
The two of us will take Exit 7 directly
to B4 and rescue the civilians.
If it gets too dangerous,
you head down there, as well.
Though, if I can be greedy,
I hope that by the time we reunite,
the veil will be lifted,
the civilians will be freed,
and we'll know what our
opponent on B5 is after.
Don't worry, Mei-san.
21:03 Tokyo Metro, Meiji Shrine Station, B2F
I won't lose anymore.
What are you looking at?
Y-You're a j-juchu... j-jujuchu...
juju... jujutsu sorcerer, right?
A jujutsu sorcerer, right?
Right?
I'm clever.
The patchfaced cursed spirit is here, right?
Where is he?
Patch... face? Patchface?
The one with stitches all over his face.
Don't insult me! I know that much!
I'm clever!
Mahito is below.
I'm here protecting the veil.
Mahito...
I think Junpei called him that, too...
No, its name doesn't matter right now.
Barriers are pretty complicated, yeah.
There are plenty of people who
are strong and still can't do them.
Though I'm both strong and capable.
This thing is responsible for
the veil? Both of them?
Doesn't seem likely...
Mahito's sorcery is bad.
He did say he was "protecting the veil."
Which makes that object very suspicious.
I'll smash it for starters.
Did you know?
The humans he transfigures
lose their flavor.
I'm clever, so I can tell the difference!
All of you need to stop
underestimating humans.
I take it y-you're not clever, huh?
You don't know what curse I am, do you?
Did you know?
The not-clever ones die first in this world.
You look just like one
Huh? You're a grasshopper curse, right?
Huh?!
This guy...
is clever!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Locust plague.
A large-scale disaster arising
from an outbreak of locusts.
The locusts will consume not just crops,
but paper, clothes, buildings—
anything and everything
made from plant fibers.
A locust is required to eat its own
weight in food every day to grow,
so a locust swarm weighing one ton
must consume 2,500 people's
worth of food each day.
The abnormal sounds of chewing fill the
air around the swarm all day and night,
and once the swarm has passed,
it leaves behind a wasteland covered
in the black fluid secreted by locusts,
creating a sight that is far from tranquil.
Mankind has long feared, hated,
and cursed such demonic pests.
What an incredible jaw and jump.
The fact that it can understand speech
means it's decently powerful, too, right?
You keep just running away...
Which is it with you?
He probably doesn't have any tricks.
Which what?
Are you clever?
Or not clever?
I'm... clever.
Clever people wouldn't really go
around calling themselves clever.
Really?!
Time to go fist-to-fist.
Your two arms
versus my four.
My arms, my jaw, and my eyes
are all superior to those of humans.
So why?
Why am I the only one getting hit?
Still, I am the more clever one!
Locusts lay their eggs underground.
To facilitate this, they're capable of extending
their abdomens, the tips of which are hard,
to nearly three times their normal length.
I win.
He did have a trick.
But more importantly...
You've eaten people.
You're prepared for what that means, right?
There was a gap in their strength
that no trick could overcome.
Nee-sama.
Yes.
The veil is lifted.
Let's wait for Itadori-kun
and then descend to B5.
21:14\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTokyo Metro, Meiji Shrine Station
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hB5F Shin-toshin Line Platform
Ko-guy was exorcised, huh?
That means a skilled sorcerer is here.
Meiji Shrine (Harajuku)
What a shame.
I wanted to fight them, too.
But I can't, huh?
Got a job to do.
21:15\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTokyo Metro, Meiji Shrine Station B4F
Impressive, Itadori-kun.
What was?
To be honest, I thought you
would struggle a bit more.
You're practically a first-grade already.
I haven't seen anyone get this far
without a technique since Kusakabe.
It wasn't Patchface.
If I'd been fighting him,
it wouldn't have gone as easily.
Nee-sama is praising you! Just accept it!
Thank you! I'm honored!
Guess we're too late.
Hey, you over there!
Are you okay?
Where are the other...
You don't need to do all this. I won't run.
I mean, if I ran, you guys would
kill every human in here, right?
That's the whole reason
I came here for you.
What are those two talking about?
Don't you mean "four"?
If you ran, huh? The correct answer is...
Do you understand when Satoru Gojo is
able to utilize his power to the fullest?
Quit with the build-up and say it.
Well, it's...
when he's alone.
The correct answer is...
Stop it!
Whether you run or not.
Get back or you'll die.
Ah, so they sealed the exit
off earlier to create a blind
Bang
Can't Break It
Eek!
so I wouldn't know if there were
people on the other side or not.
Any jujutsu sorcerer with him
is basically just a hindrance.
So we'll go one step lower and completely
surround him with non-sorcerers.
Blood Manipulation: Slicing Exorcism.
The minimum output of his cursed technique
reversal is double that of his amplification.
It'll be nearly impossible for him to use it
without catching non-sorcerers in it, too.
He probably won't be able to charge his
Blue up to an effective output, either.
It should prove difficult for him to use
Blue for high-speed movement, as well.
It would make him a dump truck as
far as non-sorcerers are concerned.
Get hit and it's instant death.
So in that situation, Satoru Gojo will
have to focus his energy on defense.
Hmph
Domain Amplification!
Makes sense.
I suppose you would think of
that after allying with curse users.
Domain Amplification...
It's the same principle as the
New Shadow School's simple domain.
They envelop themselves with the domain.
While that reduces its
guaranteed-hit effect,
it ensures they neutralize
any technique used.
That would allow their attacks to hit me.
What do we do about his
domain, Infinite Void?
The only ones unaffected by Infinite Void are
Satoru Gojo himself and anyone he touches.
Even if he does have the skill
to selectively trap you all in it,
Veil
a great number of non-sorcerers
would get crushed
to death in the space left
between his domain and the veil.
Infinite Void
Ack!
Chances are 99% that he won't use his domain.
But that means you mustn't
use your domains, either.
If you draw a large mass of
non-sorcerers into your domain,
he'll be forced to give up
on them and use his, too.
And you already realize that you can't
win a tug-of-war of domains, right?
At any rate, you just need
to get Satoru Gojo to focus.
Focus on defeating cursed spirits
and rescuing non-sorcerers.
Hey, stand up!
Come on, keep it together!
You're okay!
Come on, take my hand.
I thought I told you not to run.
Can you not understand unless I do this?
Man...
Honestly, I'm shocked.
What? Making excuses?
Not at all, baldy.
I'm saying I'm shocked that you ever thought
you could beat me if this is all you've got.
I'll want you to hold out
for at least twenty minutes.
After that, it's time for me
and the Prison Realm.
Time for the Yamanote Line Game!
The topic is Satoru Gojo's good points!
Yay!
Strong!
Only strong!
Next time, "Shibuya Incident - Gate, Open."
Next Episode
Shibuya Incident - Gate, Open
He's rich, you know.
Oh, you're such a kidder, Sensei!
Seriously, don't discount what she said.